amica.com 2007-07-18

# Amica Insurance | Amica Insurance Privacy Pledge

Your privacy is important to us. It is a policy of the Amica Companies to maintain appropriate confidentiality with regard to all information obtained in the course of our business, whether it be postal mail, telephone, fax, or Internet. Amica maintains this Privacy Policy in accordance with state and Federal Law.

Our site uses forms for visitors and policyholders to request information, products, and services. We collect the IP address of visitors to our Web pages, the E-mail address of those who communicate with us via E-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is collected only when customers/visitors voluntarily provide it. We collect PII so that we can offer you a more personalized Web experience, which may include receiving relevant content and product offerings. 

Contact information received from submitted forms is used to support our normal business activities. This includes accepting or servicing insurance policies and sending you information from time to time about new or existing products and services. 

When requesting a quote, we require information such as contact information (name, E-mail address) and unique identifiers (driver's license numbers, automobile or home information). We also collect contact information (name, mailing address) when filing a claim or requesting information from Amica. 

Background checks such as the ordering of Motor Vehicle Reports are not requested on behalf of individuals who have requested only an on-line policy quote. However, where allowed by regulation, credit-related insurance scores are requested on behalf of individuals in order to provide each with our most accurate on-line policy quote. In order to apply for and secure policy coverage, customers must contact Amica and request it. 

Our web server automatically recognizes the IP address of every visitor to our web site. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to analyze trends. 

The information we collect from this site is only used by Amica to conduct Amica business and is not shared with third parties for their use. 

To prevent unauthorized access and maintain data accuracy, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on-line.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can:

Listed within the "Contact Us" section – located on our home page – are many forms you can use to update your contact information or communicate with us, e.g., to notify us of a new address or a new car. These forms include: Change of Address, Report a New Vehicle, Report Other Changes, and Request a Call. If you would like to notify us by telephone, you can call an Amica office at 1-800-24-Amica. 

This site does not offer a way to delete/deactivate your data.

If at some point in the future there is a change to our information usage practices that affect your personal information, it will be reflected in the privacy policy date posted at the top of this page.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
